=No.9 Hunter=
=Episode 3=
Where are we?
You're back to normal.
(Why am I a woman again?)
(It seems the Stone Curse
is affected by him,)
(causing Yin-Yang imbalance.)
(My form keeps shifting.)
Do you feel like...
We're slowly losing our senses.
No! We've fallen into
the Deceit Beast's barrier.
If we don't break it soon,
we'll be consumed in here.
A barrier...
Every barrier has its core.
Found it.
This is ancient divine script.
The Wind God Chronicle says
only an ancient divine artifact
can break it.
(Isn't that me?)
Are you alright?
(Young Taoist, you can't die.)
(If you die, what do I eat?)
It's broken.
How did you decipher the stele?
I am one with the Divine Stone.
Of course I could break it.
Still, I never expected
a Deceit Beast
to possess such a treasure.
Your hand.
Pretty.
Amazing.
The pain is gone.
You're not bad.
This is pretty.
Thanks.
You just saved me.
(I saved you so I can eat you.)
(Young Taoist.)
I can sense the Deceit Beast. Let's go.
Demon.
What did you do to those brides?
I sent them home.
Home?
Do you know the truth
about this village?
This is Demon Essence.
It stores everything
the demon saw and knew.
Countless women
were persecuted by this village.
Those villagers are not innocent.
- They called it ghost weddings,
- (Mother! Save me!)
but they were trafficking
and imprisoning women.
They tortured them to death.
You think you're serving justice,
but you're actually helping the wicked.
Their crimes
are for human law to judge.
But you used your power to harm people.
By law, you must die.
Just because he is a demon,
even doing good is wrong?
You'd still kill him?
A demon
is still a demon.
His cause may be just,
but his actions are bloody and violent.
He defies the heavenly order.
It can't be forgiven.
When evil like this exists,
I have the right
to fight fire with fire.
You stand on your moral high ground,
preaching the divide
between humans and demons,
judging right and wrong.
Aren't you just another oppressor?
If order is written in blood,
how is that different from evil?
If order collapses,
good and evil become meaningless.
Fighting fire with fire
only fuels more hate
and creates greater evil.
This demon...
I must take him.
Your so-called order,
is just their cover-up.
And my path
is to overturn this very order.
The Deceit Beast's sting can control
whoever it pierces.
It can take over his mind
and make the bite mark appear.
I still can't control my heart.
Love unfulfilled.
Blows unstruck.
You two are trapped
in this love-hate entanglement.
It's your tribulation.
It is sin.
(Why hasn't the bite mark appeared?)
(Let me figure this out.)
No.
Why does the full moon have to come now?
I've been using the Stone's power
too often lately.
The backlash is hitting hard.
Forget it. I'm eating him.
No bite mark.
What if I can't break the Curse?
This male form is useful after all.
It eases the Curse's backlash.
The bite mark.
Now's my chance.
I'll drain your Spirit Essence.
Kill her!
(No.)
(I forgot the Deceit Beast's sting)
(can cloud a person's mind)
(and make them bloodthirsty.)
Kill!
Kill! Kill!
This is bad.
I can't hold the Curse back.
I think I'm a woman again.
You fool Taoist, wake up!
Stop fighting!
Kill!
(Then, I...)
(have to kill you.)
Kill!
(This is bad.)
I eat.
Ow! That's hard.
Hungry again?
It's all that Deceit Beast's fault.
That sting of his
has way too much staying power.
Where's the Deceit Beast?
I let it go.
Let it go?
Mm.
You let it go?
Thank you.
Mm.
You were testing me last night,
weren't you?
I'm a Taoist.
Keeping him would have put me in a bind.
But after everything that has happened,
I see you're not an evil demon.
Letting him go was the right call.
But you stung me with that thing.
What was your plan?
What was my plan?
To kill you.
Happy now?
Tch.
You couldn't do it.
I don't know
where you get that confidence.
Do you still remember
when you were a kid,
you were bitten by something
really, really, really cute?
Really, really cute.
Like a kitten or a puppy?
Why do I even bother asking.
You're hopeless.
You really don't remember?
No.
Sigh.
(The bite mark.)
(Does it only appear
when we're... intimate?)
(Pfft!)
(What a lousy setup.)
(Is it always
just about lovey-dovey stuff?)
(Can't we have something that shows)
(how brilliant and exceptional I am?)
You...
What's your name?
My name,
you'd better remember it.
I am Shangguan Ziyan.
Alright, Miss Ziyan.
I will remember it.
Mm.
(If it cures the Stone Curse,)
(a little intimacy is nothing.)
(Young Taoist, I've got you.)
Alright.
Miss Ziyan.
Big-eared Taoist.
♪I drink the rain of this mortal world,
and seek the path I chose♪
♪How much sorrow and joy have I known?♪
♪With this flesh and blood,
I chase the distant light♪
♪Just to see clearly
the memories of this drifting life♪
♪Let the wind sweep away
this heavy air of sorrow♪
♪Do not forget the tangled path♪
♪that you and I have crossed♪
♪Let towering waves come crashing down,
I'll fight against the tide♪
♪I shatter
the hollow fate they wrote for me♪
♪With a heart free of regret,
I'll face the heavens and earth♪